And a good Monday morning to major trouble for Americans
trying to get online this morning with Amazon at the
center of it all it's October 20th,
this is today.
Breaking overnight massive outage an issue with Amazon web
services takes down some of the world's most popular websites
and apps everything from Venmo and snapchat to ring devices and
fast food orders this morning the search for answers and how
long it will take to get everything up and running again.
Airport chaos a new round of flight delays overnight tied to
staffing problems from the government shut down some of
the nation's busiest airports impacted Newark Atlanta,
Chicago and Dallas air traffic controllers now facing a 20th
working day without pay the frustrated they deserve to be
treated better everything you need to know before heading to
the airport today and where the standoff on Capitol Hill stands
now.
Security scare the FBI investigating a
suspicious hunting stand discovered near
the Palm Beach airport with direct
sightline to Air Force one of the latest
on that and the massive no Kings anti
Trump protests in cities and towns
nationwide.
And this morning the president's online
response with a not so subtle message to
demonstrators a live report from the White House straight ahead.
Plane problems new this morning,
a cargo jet skidding off a
runway and into the water leading a frantic rescue
operation more on that plus new details on this scare in the
air.
A lithium battery blame for sparking a mid flight fire in
an overhead bin the crews quick action that saved lives and the
takeaway for all passengers bringing rechargeable devices
on board.
Brazen heist the loop temporarily closed after a
shocking daylight
robbery thieves stealing some of France's
priceless crown jewels and still on the run this morning or live
with details on the investigation and the race to
track down the suspects.
Those stories plus royal fallout scandal-plagued Prince Andrew
gives up his remaining titles and honors just ahead what it
means to the rest of the royal family.
And San Francisco.
49ers score late to seal a big Sunday night win over the
Falcon but the game of the day.
The Broncos historic 4th quarter rally
to stun the Giants on the very last play.
The highlights from an action packed day
in the NFL today Monday October 20th 2025.
From NBC News.
This is today with Savannah Guthrie and Greg Melvin
from studio one a in Rockefeller Plaza.
That's how you start a Monday happy to have you with us
starting week with us and we've got the fan fest out in the
Plaza, yes, first time ever.
The biggest fans that coming from all over the country to
get outside and celebrate with them we've got giveaways we've
got stars yeah,
a bit more to spend all 4 hours outside this
morning,
we'll get look and get out there in just a bit,
but
let's catch up on some major outages and delays impacting
nearly every one of us this morning.
We have a live look
right now at lax we want to show you it's just one of several
airports starting off the week with some major delays.
The FAA
saying it's all because of staffing issues from the
government shutdown now entering day 20.
Some breaking news those issues with Amazon Web services
experienced massive outage it's hit hundreds of popular websites
and apps maybe you notice this morning.
Take a look at this
down detector this monitors outages you can see everything
from Amazon dot com to Venmo McDonald's all impacted and
this is Brian Chung has been covering overnight the latest
this is really reaching a lot of folks this morning Brian
yeah,
absolutely and for what it's worth Amazon does say that
they have made a resolution they identified the issue that
basically recovery should be happening right now,
but it's been a weird morning for a lot of people that been
trying to access everything from finance apps to ride hailing to
their airlines as well as canva this is by the way a big type
of software that a lot of students use so it's impacting your
ability to get your homework last minute before you get started
on this Monday take a look at all these companies that according
to down detector experience some sort of reported issues.
There are 500 companies plus that were reporting some of these
issues 4 million plus outage reports that's more than double
what you usually tend to see reported on down detector again I want
to point out that a lot of these companies that said they were affected
were now also saying that they found a resolution that things seem
to be better open AI Roblox as well as Robin Hood all saying that see
things seem to be a back fully up online as you now do we know what
happened do we know it calls it also for folks want familiar with it.
What are Amazon Web services.
Yeah,
what the US think a lot of people are surprised
way I thought Amazon just sells things on e
-commerce for a W S is their web hosting services.
It's basically something
that they that they offer to businesses
to get their companies online.
Now what came down to was some sort
of what they called DNS resolution.
Basically it's just kind of big fancy talk for the
way that when you type in an address in your URL it gets
translated up to the cloud services that Amazon
basically contracts out to get all these things online.
So again this issue appeared to begin around 3 a.m.
this morning.
It seems like as of around 7 a.m.
Eastern time now things have been resolved.
But again we'll have to see
whether or not any other companies report
and they're looking at whether this is
something intentional like a hack or just an accident.
Yeah, we haven't heard from
Amazon exactly why this happened we did
reach out to comment haven't heard back
but of course a lot of memories over
that crowd strike Microsoft issue last
year which Bricks computers around the
world people remembering that big blue
screen of death not necessarily the case
here the scope a little bit smaller on
this but of course a lot of big
companies a lot of big apps people were
having issues seeing the ring doorbells
people we couldn't even get on the
Amazon website itself.
So again this is kind of hitting a lot of different types
of companies but again as of right now
it appears like Amazon says that they've
been able to mitigate the end.
Benmo too if you're late paying the babysitter.
Wait a few more hours.
All right Brian thank you.
AWS was shut down the government still
shut down to now entering a new week.
Now day 20 of the standoff making it
one of the longest in history so far.
And there's still no end in sight.
And this morning it's causing even more chaos
and delays at major airports across the country.
NBC's
chief Capitol Hill correspondent Ryan Nobles joins
us with the latest on the shutdown Ryan good morning.
Hey Greg good morning.
You're right.
This is
now the 4th week of the federal government shutdown
and the divide is as great as it was before it began.
The two sides are still not
talking and the impacts are only growing across the country.
This morning the government shutdown
causing air traffic delays across the
country.
Air traffic controller staffing issues
leading to delays at a number of
airports overnight according to the FAA
from the East Coast including Newark and
Philadelphia to Atlanta to Chicago to Dallas.
During the government shutdown air
traffic controllers considered essential
workers have been working without pay.
Transportation secretary Sean Duffy says
some are working six days a week and 50
plus hours.
They're frustrated.
They deserve to be treated better.
While some
federal employees work without pay many others put on unpaid
leave and now those impacts being felt throughout the government.
The federal agency that oversees America's nuclear stockpile
will furlough most of its staff today with about 1400 going
on leave and fewer than 400 remaining to guard the stockpile.
An energy department spokesperson telling CNN
while in Washington there's still no end in
sight to the partisan stalemate.
Many Democrats calling for the president to be more involved.
He's not taking it seriously.
We will get out of this shutdown within a matter of days
or hours once the president engages.
Democrats have been holding out for a deal on health
care specifically extending subsidies for
plans offered under the Affordable Care Act.
President Trump and Republicans are opposed to that.
We're not going to destroy our health
care for the Democrats.
The House not even in session as the two parties battle.
I refuse
to allow us to come back and engage in anything
until the government's reopened when the Democrats
do the right thing for the people.
Democrats continue to insist that President Trump is
the key to unlocking a breakthrough on the
shutdown but he's showing no signs of getting
directly involved.
In fact he's invited Republican senators
to the White House tomorrow for lunch
to take thank them for holding the line and
ushering through his administration's appointments.
Craig.
All right Ryan Nobles thank you.
We move now to an intensifying FBI investigation
in Florida after the Secret Service uncovered
a suspicious hunting stand near the Palm Beach
Airport where Air Force One frequently lands.
That discovery coming on the same weekend
that millions of Americans took part in nationwide
no Kings rallies against the Trump administration.
NBC's Garrett Hake joins us from the White House with all of this.
Garrett good morning.
Hey Savannah good morning.
And yeah the discovery of that hunting stand in the woods near
Palm Beach Airport really raising concerns for a president
who has already been the target of two assassination attempts.
But the president's weekend trip to Florida went off without
a hitch as around the country millions of demonstrators
gathered to protest the president they say is acting like a
President Trump back at the White House after a weekend trip.
House after a weekend trip to Florida.
The FBI investigating a suspicious hunting stand
found in a tree near Palm Beach International
Airport that has a direct sight line to where
the president would have exited Air Force
One.
A spokesperson for the Secret Service says
agents discovered the stand last Thursday
before Mr. Trump's arrival in Florida Friday.
A senior official familiar with the investigation
said the stand was about 200 yards away from
an area where Air Force One does not normally park.
But the plane did park there on Friday
due to construction.
Three sources familiar with the matter say the suspicious stand may
have been there for months.
And investigators are now looking at several possibilities,
including whether it's an old hunting stand,
a perch used by a photographer,
or a possible
threat.
President Trump faced two assassination
attempts during his 2024 campaign.
Walk straight back!
Meanwhile,
the president is continuing to push the limits of his power to crack
down on what he calls out of control crime and illegal immigration.
Late Sunday,
he repeated his promise to deploy the military to San Francisco.
Well,
we're going to go into San Francisco at
some point in the not too distant future,
make that a great city again.
The president's deployment of federal troops in
American cities fueling no kings demonstrations
nationwide Saturday,
with massive crowds gathering from coast to coast.
The rule of law is being destroyed.
Rallying against the Trump presidency.
Organizers said nearly seven million people
turned out at more than 2,700 demonstrations
nationwide.
The president asked about the rallies late Sunday.
I'm not a king.
I work my ass off to make our country great.
That's all it is.
I'm not a king at all.
Mr. Trump also taunting demonstrators on social media,
sharing two AI-generated videos depicting himself as a king,
in one which NBC News is choosing not to show,
dumping what appears to be raw sewage on protesters.
And on the flight back last night,
the president talked more about those federal troop deployments,
saying he was looking at other cities beyond San Francisco,
but declining to reveal which which ones also again
floating using the Insurrection Act that 1800s
law as part of his so-called crackdown on crime.
Savannah.
Garrett Haake at the White House.
Thank you, Garrett.
Let's turn to the global hotspot of Ukraine.
Now this morning we are learning more about President
Trump's White House meeting with Ukraine's leader.
We're also learning more about his phone call
with Russia's Vladimir Putin and what each side now
says it will take to end their years-long war.
NBC's chief international correspondent,
Keir Simmons,
is in Moscow for us this morning.
Keir, good morning.
Great, good morning to you.
These are crunch days,
crucial days for the war in Ukraine.
Just in the past few hours,
the Kremlin has accused Kiev of sending
contradictory messages about a possible peace deal.
This morning,
President Trump pushing for peace in Ukraine.
Let's go home, stop killing people and be done.
Secretary of State Marco Rubio is expected to meet with
Russian officials this week to plan a high stakes second summit
between President Trump and President Putin in Budapest.
Despite a Washington Post report citing two
senior administration officials familiar with
last week's call,
that the Russian leader demanded major territorial concessions,
including full
control of the Donetsk region in exchange for peace.
Russia currently controls a large portion of land in eastern Ukraine,
and President
Trump appeared to suggest on Air Force One that
Ukraine could have to make some concessions.
78 percent of the land is already taken by Russia.
You leave it the way it is right now.
They can negotiate something later on down the line.
In an exclusive interview with Meet the Press,
Ukrainian President Vladimir Zelensky rejecting
any agreement that would give Russia more
land than its forces currently hold and saying
a ceasefire must come before negotiations.
These talks have to be in quiet situation,
not under missiles,
not under drones.
Zelensky met with President Trump in Washington,
hoping to persuade the U.S.
to send long-range
Tomahawk missiles to Ukraine,
which now seems unlikely.
The President of the United States is trying
to ensure that America's security is taken
care of first,
and obviously that means that we need
to have the critical weapons system
for our own military.
Russia has bombed Ukraine nearly every day
since the last time Trump and Putin met in
Alaska in August,
Ukraine fighting back over the weekend,
using drones to strike a vital
Russian gas plant.
But Zelensky says a diplomatic end to the war may still be possible.
Do you think President Trump can end the war in Ukraine?
God bless.
God bless, yes.
And President Zelensky telling Kristen Welker
that he would be prepared to attend that summit,
saying, how can a deal be done without us?
But Craig, that is not something that President
Putin in the Kremlin behind me there would relish.
Craig?
Our chief international correspondent on the ground in Russia,
Forrest Kear Simmons,
thank
you.
More news to cover this morning,
including major scares,
plural involving planes,
a new
one just overnight after a weekend that saw
a packed Air China flight forced to make an
emergency landing
after a lithium battery sparked a fire that erupted in an overhead
bin.
You see it right there.
You see Stephanie Gask is here with more on all this.
Hi, Steph.
Good morning.
Hey, good morning, Savannah.
Yeah,
some scary moments for travelers and
airline crew in multiple incidents overseas,
including a deadly landing in Hong Kong,
one of the largest and busiest airports in the world.
This morning,
terrifying scenes in the skies and on the ground.
Dramatic video from Hong Kong showing a cargo plane in the
water after it skidded off the airport's runway early Monday,
colliding with a patrol vehicle.
While the crew survives,
two airport workers were killed.
Authorities say the aircraft snapped
in half as it careened into the sea.
Meanwhile,
at 30,000 feet,
another alarm for flyers,
a fire believed to be caused by a battery breaking out in the
middle of an Air China flight as passengers watch in horror.
Flight attendants seen rushing to respond.
The flight was about 45 minutes into its planned trip from Hangzhou,
China to Seoul,
but had to make an emergency landing in Shanghai.
The airline later saying the fire was caused by a lithium battery,
which spontaneously combusted,
adding no injuries were reported.
It's just the latest onboard battery fire this year.
In January,
a power bank was blamed for engulfing this Air
Busan plane in flames and injuring seven people.
While in May,
a charger appeared to overheat and smoke in a
seat back during a Southwest Airlines flight.
Oh, position.
We have an emergency inbound with reported fire in the cabin.
Soon after,
the company began requiring passengers to keep all
portable chargers and battery packs visible during flight.
Experts say the potential fire risk
increases when lithium batteries are damaged,
charging or are stored in high temperatures.
According to the FAA,
there have been more than 60 lithium
battery air incidents so far this year,
more than half of those caused by
battery packs and e-cigarettes or vapes.
Still,
with these types of batteries found in almost every portable device,
safety experts say airlines should consider more regulations.
Just leaving it to the public has proven not to be adequate.
Experts say the potential fire risk
increases when lithium batteries are damaged,
charging or stored in high temperatures.
You know, don't charge your phone in your bag.
To your point,
these batteries are just about everything.
Yeah, everywhere.
Thank you, Stephanie.
All righty,
let's get a first check of the weather.
And for that,
we say good morning to Dylan,
who's in for Alex.
Looks like we're looking at some rain already,
huh?
Good morning, yes.
But the rain for us here is almost on the way out.
It's going to move up across New England.
We still have some heavier rain back through central Pennsylvania,
western New York right now.
It's this area of low pressure that's going to pull away.
Behind it,
it gets a little bit breezy and temperatures drop,
so it is going to get cooler as the day goes on.
We also have this cold front that's going to bring some
scattered showers and nuisance storms to parts of the Great Lakes
as we go through this afternoon and then tomorrow afternoon,
too.
As for rainfall totals,
about one to three inches,
mostly up across Vermont and New Hampshire,
up across Maine,
as that storm continues to exit the New England area.
That's a good weather across the country.
We'll get to your local forecast in the next 30 seconds.
Next will take it himself on first and 10.
He's able to get back now 730 with a comeback for the ages by
those Denver Broncos Denver scoring all 33 of their points
in the 4th quarter.
Watched it live unfold last night.
They
beat the New York Giants in the last second field goal.
You just
saw their 33 to 32 and then on Sunday night football Christian
McCaffrey he scored two touchdowns as the San Francisco
49ers doubled up the Atlanta Falcons 20 to 10 big day of
football yesterday,
but the Giants went out of their way to
lose that.
I mean that wasn't just a win.
That was a rewriting
of NFL history,
the most amount of points scored in the 4th
quarter by a team that had previously been shut out for
3 quarters and Jackson darts face there.
That's how Giants
fans are feeling.
We want to talk about the projects.
Yeah,
wow we should talk about the Raiders can't talk about that
either.
To get to this morning,
a busy half hour ahead starting
with the stunning heist at the world's most visited museum it
was opening yet the taking just minutes to steal priceless
jewels once worn by French royalty and make a getaway
NBC's Molly hunters there in Paris for us Molly good
morning what happened.
Guys good morning this was sending good morning from a
very windy Paris now this is day 2 of a major investigation
we're told there are 60 detectives working the case and
the story authorities excuse me say there were likely 4
thieves and they were slick well-trained professionals this
morning the most visited museum in the world in the heart of Paris
remains shuttered on Sunday morning a brazen daylight heist
just 30 minutes after the Louvre open to the public and this
morning the thieves still on the run the interior minister says
the experienced crew of thieves use this electric ladder
mounted on the back of a truck to get to the second floor balcony
and once the thieves reach that second floor
balcony the interior ministry says they broke
the glass window with grinders you can see it boarded up right
now as the alarm sounded their target like gallery depth along
home to the French crown jewels and crown diamonds the thieves
smashed to display cabinets according to the culture ministry
as you can see in this video widely published in French
media this man wearing a high vis vest they stole 9 priceless
items in all including sapphire and emerald necklaces earrings
and tiaras including one that belonged to fashion icon Empress
Jeanette Napoleon the third wife in the gallery
the thieves left behind the massive 140 karat
region diamond in the getaway they dropped
the Empress's diamond encrusted crown found
outside the museum the whole operation took just
7 minutes the thieves got away on motorbikes
the incident so dramatic like a scene out of
the netflix show looping the necklace belonged
to Marie Antoinette we're gonna steal it as
soon as the robbery started quick thinking
museum staff called the police and
started evacuating visitors lots of
confusion lots of misdirection did they
ran us all out they would say go this way
and that would be closed when you rob
the Louvre that's a big deal to all of
France French president Emmanuel Macron
called it an attack on a heritage we
cherish because it's our history but
it's not the first time thieves have
targeted the Louvre back in 1911 the
Mona Lisa was stolen by a museum employee
but returned two years later much more
famous today authorities say they'll
stop at nothing to recover the stolen
jewels this is a huge deal but guys it's
also shaping up to be a major political
scandal so French media are reporting on
a leaked audit report not yet published
that reportedly found that the Louvre
routinely tightened the security budget
in recent years the other big question
that we all have is who is buying these
priceless stolen jewels guys all right
Molly good question for our next guest
former FBI agent Robert Whitman who
founded the agency's rapid deployment are crime team
during his career help recover 300 million dollars worth of
art and cultural property rather the perfect guest for this
moment,
first of all I I was just surprised that it was
apparently so easy to break into the Louvre in broad daylight.
Yeah,
you know the the point there was I think people
thought that these guys were working at the Louvre numbers
they were doing some type of construction.
Yeah, they could
make that noise and people would think must be normal
because I can't be a robbery in the daytime.
Yeah.
And they
were wearing the yellow construction
vests I've seen that before I was
involved in an undercover investigation
when a group stole paintings from a
museum in Nice and they were doing the
same thing they had the same kind of
overall coveralls all like they were
employees and they made their getaway on
mopeds it's a it's a pretty common way
of escaping in Europe because of the easy
ability to navigate through the traffic
and so they can get away quickly.
Sounds
like you think this is probably at least partly an inside job to
Molly's point there when you steal millions of dollars worth
of jewels from the Louvre you don't just go into a pawn shop
so it's like how do you how do you what do they do with it.
Well they are going to look at it.
We hope that they're going
to try to sell it.
Yeah, there's different ways that
they'll try to monetize this is what it's all about making
money.
So the worst way would be is if they melt it down.
They'll pop all the diamonds pop the
gems and try to sell them one by one.
Have you checked 47th Street here.
That's where that could happen.
It could be.
But I think that that's the worst situation.
The best case scenario is maybe they
come around and try to ransom them back.
And what will happen there is possibly a you know the
country of France might offer a reward for information.
If you're going to do a crime the way you get
away with it is by doing it by yourself leaving no
evidence in this case.
And thirdly don't tell no one.
In this case it was a group of people.
So there's more than one person.
They left a lot of forensic evidence behind.
And basically I'm going to tell you they're
going to tell people that they did it.
So when this reward number comes out you're going to have
people calling in saying you know we know something about this.
They're going to catch.
Robert quickly what does this stand in sort of
the history of like thefts that you've seen.
This is how big of a deal is this.
This is audacious.
This is probably the fourth gold theft
I've seen in the past few years in Europe.
Just a month ago September 17th the Natural History
Museum in Paris was hit again just like this.
Using cutters all the same M.O.
and they stole a bunch of nuggets of gold worth about 600000 euros.
So I think if I was an investigator on this
case I'd be looking at that and this and seeing
similarities thing and there might be an organized group
out there and the price of gold is so high right now so a lot of
motivation.
Robert thank you so much to have you here appreciate
it.
I still have a good highlights from Sabrina
Carpenter's double duty shift over to SNL plus the star set
to make their hosting debuts in the weeks ahead.
First off some new details on Prince Andrew's decision to
give up his remaining titles and the new accusations about
his ties to Jeffrey Epstein what it means for him and what
it means for the royal family have a live
report from Buckingham Palace right after this.
We're back 7.42 the latest chapter now in Prince Andrew's
fall from grace the royal has now surrendered the use of his
title the Duke of York it follows explosive new allegations
in the posthumous memoir of Jeffrey Epstein's most vocal
accuser NBC's Raph Sanchez joins us now from Buckingham
Palace with the latest on the fallout raff good morning.
Guys good morning from a rainy London Prince Andrew has always
denied having sex with one of Epstein's trafficking victims but this
scandal has haunted the royal family for years now Andrew step
back from royal duties back in twenty nineteen now he's giving up
use of his official titles and we are learning more about the role
that Prince William played behind the scenes in that decision.
This morning revelations and allegations about
Prince Andrew's links to convicted sex offender
Jeffrey Epstein rocking the royal family Andrew
announcing he's giving up use of his official
titles like the Duke of York and his royal
highness out of a new Virginia Ju Fre memoir
being published this week Ju Fre says she
was forced to have sex with Andrew when she
was seventeen after being trafficked by Epstein
King Charles's younger brother saying in part
in discussion with the king and my immediate
and wider family we've concluded the continued
accusations about me distract from the work of his
majesty and the royal family adding I vigorously
deny the accusations against me.
NBC News has learned that Prince William as heir to the throne
was consulted about Andrew's decision before it was made public.
I think that knowing his uncle
is connected to so many allegations
means he absolutely doesn't want him to be standing alongside
other working members of the family.
It comes as British police say they are actively investigating
media reports that Andrew asked a police bodyguard
to look into Ju Fre back in 2011. Buckingham Palace
declined to comment.
I have no recollection of ever meeting this lady.
Ju Fre who died by suicide in
April spoke with Savannah in 2019. The abuse
went on for a little bit in the bathroom and
then it continued to the bedroom and I just couldn't believe it.
I couldn't believe that
even royalty were involved.
I thought they had standards that they had
to live by.
Ju
Fre's new book published after her death
claims she had sex with Andrew three times.
Her family
releasing this statement.
We the family of Virginia Roberts Ju Fre believe that Prince
Andrew's decision to give up his titles is
vindication for our sister and survivors everywhere.
And Ju Fre's family are calling on King Charles
to go further and strip Andrew of his title
of prince.
Now that isn't something the king can do
without ripping up the entire rulebook
but it is clear both the royal family and
the public here in the UK have lost patience
with Andrew and there is now mounting pressure on him to move
out of his royal residence near Windsor Castle.
Guys.
Raph Sanchez from Buckingham Palace.
Raph thank you.
All right let's switch gears get another check
of the weather from Dylan who's in for our
hi, Dylan.
Good morning again everybody.
It is pretty quiet across the country today.
We have a
couple of spots with some scattered showers,
some isolated storms.
Most of the real heavy
rain will be across central and northern
New England as this storm pulls away.
It's breezy
and cool otherwise nice and mild back through
the Midwest in the 60s and 70s. Beautiful
out west too.
Lots of sunshine highs in the 70s and
80s. Let's look at the weather across
the country now.
Here's a peek out your window.
And that's your latest forecast.
Alright, Dilly Dilly, thank you very much.
Time for our PSSPL sneak peek to Pop Start,
which is coming up.
This has to do with a little nature narration.
Listen closely to this.
Despite their great size and strength,
these are gentle,
thoughtful,
problem-solving creatures.
And perhaps more relatable to us than any other great ape.
I lobbied by the way to show you 20 minutes of this,
but that's
that's what we got there that is the voice of course of Sir
David Attenborough who just became the oldest daytime Emmy
winner at 99 years old Attenborough took home the award
for outstanding daytime personality non daily for his
work on that netflix documentary secret lives of
orangutans he topped the previous record winner which
was the great Dick Van Dyke won at 98 for days of our lives
for parents, but I was thinking of your show.
Yeah, you have
that or thought us to show that you narrate and I sound exactly
a thing.
Yeah,
I mean I'm 99. Yeah,
it's a nice pisses people
yeah much more pop start just ahead plus Jenna has arrived
with the morning.
But I guess we're stepping up the countdown
to Halloween with some of the most adorable and costumed pets
you'll ever see right after this.
She's here with our second favorite part of the.
All right,
Halloween is right around the corner and everyone's
getting into the spooky spirit,
including some furry friends,
the 35th annual Tompkins square.
Dog parade took place
right here in New York yesterday and the pups showed up and
showed out celebration included pets and their owners and their
Halloween finest as they strutted the streets village.
Here's some fan favorite.
And of course,
a lot of booboo course,
but it was the serial
killers who took.
That's she said pet owners.
Yes, what they want y'all what
a year's worth of dog food.
Yes,
a lot of people haha.
I got it.
Guys I can kind of.
All right speaking of a lively crowds here.
Yeah,
yeah,
is on that hundreds of
our favorite folks out there getting out there celebrate
after your local news and weather.
It's 8 o'clock on today coming up offline Amazon Web services
reporting a major outage overnight taking down popular
websites and apps like Venmo snapchat and ring devices.
So what went wrong for live with the latest.
Then medical
breakthrough inside the new study revealing how peanut
allergies have plummeted in children,
let's talk about the
preventative measure that doctors and parents are saying
could fight off a life threatening allergy.
And fanning out we're kicking off our week-long fan fest
celebration with a fun morning on the Plaza.
You do not want to miss.
All that plus Sabrina's SNL takeover.
Steve Carell's office surprise.
Oh my God, okay, it's happening
every sick on and the spice girls ready to reunite.
Today Monday October 20th 2025.
32nd anniversary.
cancer.
A celebration.
Travel from Indianapolis.
From Prince Arkansas.
Kansas City,
Missouri.
Mount Sterling, Kentucky.
And Richmond, Virginia.
Our fifth time on the Plaza.
Today's show's number one fan.
It's Today's Fan Fest.
Yeah.
Little fan right there.
We've got a lot of the cannot wait
to get this started on Monday morning.
It's going to be a
fun-filled morning.
You surprises.
Some stars to want to join us outside as well.
The great yeah looking forward to it.
Let's get right to the
news top of the 8 o'clock we begin with that massive global
outage overnight an issue with Amazon
Web Services taking down some of the
world's most popular websites and apps
and to see Brian Chung is all over this
one of the very latest Brian good morning.
Hey good morning and Amazon does
say that this issue has been in their words fully mitigated this was
affecting basically everything from
ride-hailing apps like lift to finance
apps like Venmo in fact our co-workers
here at NBC we even had an issues
getting onto slack as a reminder Amazon
is not just about e-commerce they host a
number of websites for companies through the cloud there wasn't
a specific clarification from Amazon on exactly why this happened
but this particular product that they have they have over 1 million
customers as a reminder they actually make more income off of
this Amazon Web Services product than they do off of e-commerce
but all of this is bringing back memories of that crowd strike
Microsoft outage that bricked millions of computers around the world
all of this underscoring the fragility of the Internet and all
of this technology despite the fact that we are in this age of AI
it is kind of a sobering reminder that it only takes a few issues
for a lot of people to have problems I read a little while ago that
half the Internet was down at one point and I think Savannah mentioned
this earlier but just remind folks at this point in terms of bad
actors do they expect that do they think that this was nefarious in
any way yeah so again we reach out to Amazon for an exact definition
of exactly why this happened they didn't say so whether it was a
hack whether it was something else we don't know but it appears as of
right now that Amazon is able to get a lot of those websites back
online all right we'll keep watching Brian thank you jury selections
starts in Illinois this morning in the
murder trial of a now former deputy
charged with killing a woman who'd
called 911 for help body camera video
shows the final moments of Sonia
Massey's life prosecutors saying then
deputy Sean Grayson used excessive force
when he shot Massey after she picked up
a pot of boiling water and this is
Maggie Vespa joins us now from Chicago
with the latest on this case Maggie good morning.
Hey Craig good morning it has been more than a year since Sonia
Massey died in her own kitchen and media attention and protests
since prompting a judge to move these proceedings to a different
county where now this one time deputy will stand trial and
presumably jurors will watch video of that fatal shooting and to that
end a warning some of what you're about to see is disturbing.
This morning a former deputy's first degree murder trial
getting underway with jury selection set to begin in the
shooting death of 36 year old Sonia Massey.
Body camera video set to play a
pivotal role showing then Sangamon
County Sheriff's deputy Sean Grayson and
another officer arriving at Massey's
Springfield Illinois home in July of
last year after she called 911 about a
possible prowler the mother of two whose
family said she struggled with mental
health issues picks up a pot of boiling
water.
Autopsy records show he shot Massey in the head
later saying in court motions he feared for his life.
Grayson was fired and pleaded not guilty
to charges of first degree murder,
aggravated battery with a firearm and official misconduct.
His attorney consistently declining to comment.
There was no humanity there was terrible things that was
said even after the fact as she's laying there on the floor.
The shooting sparking outrage.
Records show Grayson had a history of disciplinary issues at previous
police jobs and had pleaded guilty to two DUIs one of which two
sources told NBC News caused him to be discharged from the army.
Red flags the then sheriff told me his
department's vetting process failed to unearth.
So I know you say based on what you knew
at the time it seemed like a good hire.
I'm asking based on what you know now was it a good hire?
That's that's speculation and you can't
speculate hindsight is always 2020.
He later stepped down Massey's family since obtaining a $10 million
settlement from Sangamon County all the while calling for a conviction.
Now the Sangamon County Sheriff's Office also
it's worth noting under pressure from the DOJ
earlier this year agreed to implement new hiring
and training practices as far as this trial goes
expected to last up to 2 weeks and Sean Grayson if
convicted faces the possibility of life in prison.
Maggie Vestman Chicago Force Maggie thank you.
Other news now about 60,000 children have avoided developing
peanut allergies thanks to a landmark study a decade ago that
encouraged parents to introduce peanut products to babies.
According to a new study from Children's Hospital of Philadelphia
researchers found that peanut allergies in children ages 0 to 3 declined
were expanded in 2017. The guidance calls for introducing
peanuts and other major food allergens to babies between 4
and 6 months old.
So baseball we go and it all comes down to one game tonight
between the Blue Jays and the Mariners with a trip to the
World Series on the line,
Toronto staying alive the big
win last night in game 6 of the ALCS.
Addison barger to run Homer in the 3rd inning that gave the
Blue Jays a 4 run lead to run I would go on the limit 6 to 2.
A win or go home game 7 tonight.
We have a moment.
Yeah,
so it's on ahead had what's been described perhaps as the
greatest individual performance in a baseball game over the
weekend.
3 home runs 6 innings 10 strikeouts in one game.
Wow yeah, he plays you know, but you know,
I show you tiny
yeah,
I got that stuff for sure he had he had more home
runs that he allowed hits yes think about that for us 3 home
runs to hit a lot I got coming up your spice girls fan what
one member the spice was now saying what the idea of a
reunion tour that's coming up.
Plus we're launching our very first today fan fest by ourselves
in the hot seat.
Look who's here Andy Cohen he's going to
help.
Anything and everything you've ever wanted to know about the
show high and the first these messages.
Just for the today show viewers and all starts right here right
now with this big celebration on the plot.
Yes, we've got a
fun way to get things started with the to pass the mic to all
of you letting fans ask their burning questions about the
show, but we couldn't do it alone.
We called our friend,
Andy Cohen.
Of course host of Bravo's watch what happens live
we're going to do a real Housewives that reunion right
here.
Yeah,
I'm doing this we hand the mic to you.
Morning TV.
I remember Bravo con what yeah,
I mean okay guys are first
question is from Melissa and Mitch from Rhode Island stay
tuned for the real Housewives of Rhode Island,
Melissa and
Mitch, what do you got.
This come this question is for Savannah,
you've got to
interview a lot of your idols has there anyone has anyone
actually made you starstruck.
Oh yeah, I love that question.
Thank you guys.
Yes a lot a lot
of time I can very okay,
well when Harrison Ford was on yes,
I mean I literally I feel like the whole interview with me
trying to flirt with him.
I love him so much that I feel it
was receptive.
Yeah, it was very nice and I mean I'm just so
happy in that picture because he was you know,
it was like
Han solo, yeah, I just love your list of Jason.
I mean he was
receptive in a joking.
You know because you're that way with
Richard gear.
I do like to.
Yeah,
you also I'm in the bond.
Yeah, you like
that.
Savannah likes a daddy next up a question for Craig
from Kelly from Indianapolis.
Okay, Kelly.
Good morning,
Craig Kelly if this wasn't your job what other
career path would you want to follow.
Oh, it's a good question.
You know the answer this is going
to sound weird it's going to sound like a lot I probably
candle making.
I know I that a lucrative career.
Candle making.
Peace and solace of last few years and like being in my
garage.
But more candles, he does make a nice candle.
I think we know
what Craig's today show Christmas gift is I would love
what beautiful candle he does I I know it sounds weird.
I will
say I was not expect.
You never know what's going to.
Lisa from New Jersey has a question for car car.
I bring
it on.
I heard said I good how are you what's something that goes on
off camera during commercial breaks in studio one.
It would
totally surprise us watching at home.
I got to be honest.
First the first thing that happens is a lot of face timing
kids.
Yeah,
yeah,
so you guys will we all jump on our phones
a face time the kids then there immediately is an argument
about the studio temperature.
Yeah, that's true that because
you like it like you like the normal temperature you can hang
beef in studio one freezer where this got 3 here prefers it a
little more she likes it.
72 degrees.
Swear like a truck
driver during the commercial.
Yeah,
that's great question.
A lot of grazing in the kitchen.
Okay next up Bethany
and her daughter Audrey from Florida have a question about
getting ready before the show.
Hey Savannah,
I you all fashion sense is absolutely fabulous.
What your morning getting ready routine look like picking out
your outfit I need to know.
Well,
it's actually Craig as we know Craig Carson and Al who
are like the fashion he says you can be nervous.
I am I feel
like I'm just like anyone who's standing at home and looking at
the cause that be like what I wear today just to it last
minute.
Relatable Queen it's true and then do you own your
clothes or do you rent the runway.
No I have to buy him I
know the creation is not purchased that everybody.
Outfit I do of course,
yes,
of course,
some of the girls will
do like to the rental thing and then but I've always just bought
but you look great coordinate in the morning we don't we don't
but sometimes it just like today we're coordinated,
we
didn't mean to I will say that one of the things that Savannah
Guthrie will always be known for in addition to her hard in
her hard hitting interviews her shoe game strong.
You ever been
like in her dressing room and you see me shoes.
It's her shoes
off.
She was always fit like no matter what it's actually it's
you see I would say Craig and Al who are discussing fashion
because they are like.
Okay,
let's go to Zoe and family here from Ohio what's
your question for Craig.
I Craig is there a standout fan moment on the Plaza that you'll
never forget.
Oh a couple of the I think it was just a few months ago,
there's some social media trend where people are like
surprising folks on tiktok
the story of the trend and my buddy Leroy like my childhood
friend friends.
So the godfather of my son we've been friends
since the second grade is we lose class.
I turned on the
Plaza.
One of the best moments in the Plaza because it's like find
someone who looks at you the way Craig looked at Leroy it's
you know.
But I was still here is.
Okay last but not least Kate and her family from Connecticut
have a question about travel.
If this is a family went on a group vacation what everyone's
travel personality who is organizing everything who's
late for the flight and who's just there for a good time so
you know sleep.
I think I think Jenna organizes every every
and has a really fun itinerary laid out.
Yeah, I like to get
to the airport early and broker gets that by the way try out
Walker travels in a sport club.
He still travels like what that's the man something out
those la guardia back of it.
I think we get a bloody Mary.
Yeah, that's the first and then yeah.
Okay,
I'm a today fan too.
I'm you know we had a discussion
about questions back so I'm bringing it down.
I've even
censored yes,
I not really but I want to know what's an on air
blooper that you'll never repeat that will never happen again
that's a great question that's I have one my one of my big
snafus was reading a story and it was when I was new here too
I was used to the teleprompter and I said the stories about
Leonardo and I said Leonardo to crap yo.
To this day when I see a lead Leonardo's name the prompter
my heartbeat starts to.
And our the crappy.
Yeah, we have a good one.
I mean it's one that almost got a suit but there was a big week
to call years ago when I was doing this is a great and I read
that the this particular brands food had killed by 8 people and
the brand had not killed 8 people they had made 8 people
sick.
And yeah,
yeah,
I had I think I told you about this before I
asked Chloe
Kardashian like 10 seconds before we're going to break it
about the rumors that her father and she was I was so
embarrassed that I felt like all this pressure I just started
and I felt like the producers wanted me to ask this issue
question,
the very end of it and Chloe like what about this rumor that
Robert Kardashian's not really your father and they were like
10,
9,
8,
I was so embarrassed and she was such a class act
and she's like nothing to it and it was like we made the
break and I forever.
The question I asked the question I
didn't want to Chloe was a total class act.
All these years you've been doing this is there a blooper.
Oh my gosh I lean into a blooper.
You know what I was
doing a great interview with Oprah and the show was about to
end and I it yet that I am turned or and I was like you
ever swum in the lady pond.
It was like.
She said no and then Gail said she didn't get
the question.
So then not big.
Any producers you know it's Andy what can I say.
I are on the road get tickets to 2 nights in Chicago.
For 6
years, I know I can we going back out.
Anderson show.
Thank you.
It's on sale.
You know you do it was a bit like
everyone else did a little micro dose of a G L P one.
I'm not my goal.
Oprah's on the phone.
Yeah, exactly just a
couple questions.
Okay.
A fan favorite on every morning.
I will tell a
proper.
The interesting all right for Saturday.
Over the
weekend,
Sabrina Carpenter stop by studio 8 H and hosted and
also the guest musical act for an episode that included the
return of this beloved character.
The babe I promise to mingles in the past.
Came up this way.
No, I'm just kidding.
I live very close by.
Serena pulling double duty as she took over the stage for the
first live performance of her new hit song nobody's son.
the other one she did man child in like yeah,
and that
with you know no pants and kids in the room,
but she was great
and she's so talented vote.
There's been like a 1000 SNL's
less than 50 have hosted have done that double duty and so
it's rare and she did a great job with that now will return
in November with brand new lineups being announced that
includes miles teller coming back and Brandi Carlisle
last time host comedian,
Nikki Glaser is going to be on the
show musical guest somber and twister star Glenn Powell is
going to be there too so you can check that out and Olivia
Dean will be there.
Here and she is also great.
Next up the
office who remembers this heartwarming moment from the
hits.
What do you mean.
You want to buy it.
Yeah, we have to have it for the office.
All right now almost 20 years later Steve Carell is still
showing up for Jenna Fisher Krell stopped by her play in
Chicago and even surprised the audience afterwards Jenna
posting the sweet little side by side instagram caption there
that says look who came to my.
We're back with today and that
after that and off.
You know it wouldn't be a fan fest celebration without
connecting with our fans so where is Corina.
And this is your husband Gordon,
yeah,
where you guys from
Philly OK now you've got quite the signs here pictures of
everybody now how many times you actually been to the Plaza 5,
5, times 5 time here 5 times since January.
Yeah, what do
you love about coming here so much guys everyone so nice.
New York is beautiful.
It is the greatest in the end of the
shop today stages,
I mean yes,
you've done it all and you
don't mind being a part of no we absolutely love you guys and
this is a great to see in the world.
I think you guys deserve something nice for your loyalty
for coming to the today show in New York in the cold.
We have
our sponsor Miami Beach in greater Miami,
they are giving
you a trip to Miami Beach to celebrate 100 years of art deco
well this is going to be the trip for you because you and
Gordon here.
Right.
Today show we like that sort of thing.
You're going to
get round trip airfare to Miami a 3 night stay at the 5 star on
on does hotel and dinner at the hotel's restaurant there's more
you get to explore the beach and take in the sights of the
private tour of the iconic art deco architecture that Miami
Beach is famous for how do you think oh my God I feel like
it's a dream.
It's it's worth coming here all those months.
Yes, oh my.
And you were just such a sweet lady,
thank you so much.
Thank you so much.
Postcard to crack.
You know,
she is a sweet lady she's a very sweet I would
agree with you Dylan,
thank you and thank you as well for being
such a loyal loyal viewers over the years.
We're here now with
Golden Globe winner himself Oscar Isaac,
you know him from
blockbuster film franchises like do star Wars,
many more.
Well now Oscars taking on an iconic character Victor
Frankenstein in your model towards new movie Frankenstein
take a look.
I mean I was just welcome by the way you very welcome the fan
by the way I'm from Miami.
I was just telling you you know
Frank that's been around since if I'm not mistaken early
1800's it's been remade hundreds of times.
This is
Frankenstein like I had never seen it before.
It's it's more of a dynamic between a father and a son
that's what this is.
Well what makes this Frankenstein
unlike any others is Guillermo del Toro.
I mean he's a master of cinema.
He's dedicated to handcrafted you know artists
artisanal movie making like they don't make anymore.
All the sets are handmade you know and it's with a team
of artists and so it's just sumptuous it's beautiful and
he focused on the emotional aspect of fathers and sons
and the pain that gets passed down from fathers to sons.
And in this in this iteration,
it's you know Victor being the father
of this creature that he rejects.
It's also this question of who's really the monster.
Right is the monster the the creation or is the monster the creator.
Well as we know with Guillermo del Toro's movies,
he's got a real affinity for creatures for monsters for people that
feel other you know on the outside he talks about seeing Frankenstein
for the first time Boris Karloff and saying this is my patron saint of
imperfection so yes in this film you really see that
the Victor as he as he becomes more and more obsessed
as he rejects his creation as he tries to destroy it.
He becomes the monster.
I know actors have to draw inspiration from
from real life experiences for you it may not have
been that much of a stretch because I read that there
was a point in your life where you were actually
transporting dead bodies.
It's true and my dad's a doctor and
so I worked at a hospital in Miami where I was a transporter
and one of the things that to do is go down to the morgue and
you know deal with that and you see a lot of humanity actually
when I went to drama school.
I put that down as my experience
because you see so much of humanity and hospitals,
you know
all sorts of different reactions and extremities of
life.
You called working with your mother to on this project joyous
you worked with a lot of people yeah and what was it about this
particular project which was by the way is dark.
Yeah, it is
gory right what what made this choice for you.
It's the animal.
I mean we spoke exclusively in Spanish to
each other so I felt like making a movie with a family member
and he just has such a mischievous energy and
inclusive energy and and he said he's like I don't I'm
making you a banquet and if you see this movie it is a banquet
that he's made not only for me but for everybody that comes to
watch it.
We're going to have your co-star here tomorrow.
I want to read something that he recently said about you and
get your reaction to it.
Here it is this is the court,
I think we've got it's coming it's coming stand by here.
Jacob Elordi to Oscar Isaac.
One of my favorite actors in
the world.
One of one of what was it like working
with Jacob Elordi what he does and what
he plays the creature and what he does
in this movie is so heartbreaking the
second he walked on set I remember him
walking kind of fingers first because he
is what he does is so graceful and unusual and just incredibly
watch it there.
The mesmerized by what he's done for such a
young actor to have so much poise and discipline.
It's
really impressive.
You really do develop an empathy for the
creature throughout the film.
You're beautiful and thank you
so much so much here and happy fan fest to you is that you can
catch Frankenstein in select theaters now you can also catch
it on netflix November 7th up next we're going to take you
inside the game how the 49ers using what is San Francisco's
most enduring landmarks to rev up fans there sandbox to take
a sense of the game right after this because this is today on
the in the sea.
The game are seriously behind the scenes of the NFL 49ers
scored a big home win over Atlanta last night for the
faithful the excitement surrounding the game began long
before kickoff with the sounding of the team's iconic.
Yeah,
we see Sam Brock joins us you got a first first look of its kind
here Levi's Stadium and that ringing noise sound guys this was
a stroke of genius it goes back generations right it's an idea
though that really gained traction in 2012 when a
former 49ers executive was listening to the foghorn
sounding out over the San Francisco Bay and thought.
Why can't we incorporate this into our game
day experience they ultimately did guys and
now it's a 49ers staple embraced by fans and
former players alike making celebrations from
the South Bay to the city uniquely San Francisco.
It's a San Francisco foggy tradition featuring
some of the biggest icons in the Bay Area.
And for Sunday night's football game against
the Falcons.
It's guitarist Neil Shaw from the legendary group Journey the latest
in a long list of former players and rock stars energizing the sound.
That sends the fans who receive it into a complete frenzy.
We're talking about a giant foghorn producing
decibels on par with a jet engine taking off.
49ers director of game day production Laura L.J.
Johnson says that sounds can't be mistaken for anything else.
Everyone can hear it out at their tailgates.
Hey it's time to come in and be a part of kickoff and then
on scoring plays and of course my favorite time on a win.
Johnson gave us the inside story.
So all this technology in Silicon Valley.
All I need to do is walk up there and pull a lever.
Correct.
So it's cool.
This famed foghorn is actually woven into San Francisco history.
More
than 100 years ago the fog also forced hundreds of shipwrecks
on the Bay's craggy rocks including the Rio de Janeiro steamship
in February of 1901 called the Titanic of the Golden Gate.
It led to loss of life stranded passengers and a watershed moment.
The development of a foghorn system that warns mariners
about challenging visibility and endures to this day
from the Golden Gate to Niners games at Levi's Stadium.
We wanted it to be as authentic as possible right.
It's going to mimic the sounds that people hear when
you're in San Francisco when you're near the Bay.
On the field.
Robinson all the way back for a 49ers touchdown.
The Niners Walter Payton man of the
year representative linebacker Curtis
Robinson feeding off the energy.
When it goes off what does it sound like.
The best way I can describe it is it almost sounds like a battle cry.
Like if you think of like old Viking movie.
So it sounds something like this.
Yeah something like that.
The symbol so synonymous with the Niners.
It's in the latest version of Madden.
The first celebratory horn this small box ran
into some technical difficulties a few years ago.
We had alumni Patrick Willis come in for the game and
our pro football Hall of Fame linebacker very strong.
He pulled it just a little bit too hard.
That's a nice way of saying he broke it.
Yeah.
So now there's this supersized version which we got to try.
So Jerry Rice has done this.
Joe Montana has done this.
All these celebrities have done it.
And now I'm going to tell you I present to you the foghorn.
Mark that thing is not quite.
But here's a little secret.
While this ceremonial foghorn is in the spotlight
these two smaller foghorns on the North scoreboard are
the loud authentic ones that the thousands of fans
packed into Levi's Stadium actually here during games.
And those this is rarefied air back
here get punched from the control room.
If you're lucky enough to strike gold just press that button.
Hold it down.
I'm kind of emotional.
It's a lot of power.
OK. Here we go.
It's actually the perfect ball and a perfect pitch
to fire up the passion of the 49ers faithful.
And guys as you know Levi's Stadium in Santa Clara is
actually hosting the Super Bowl this year broadcast on NBC and
we did have to ask are they planning on using the foghorns.
LJ said it is at the discretion of the NFL but it is absolutely
a possibility.
We were pressing that foghorn so often neighbors
in that area were probably like what is going on the next door
chance calling law enforcement.
There's something happening.
I was a game today.
This is very bizarre.
Just had it would not
be today can test it out some shopping of course this morning
Adriana Brock is bringing us an amazing deal.
And that.
The rolls on that today editorial director Adriana
Bach here with a preview the brand sponsoring and popping up
at all of our fan fest events if you cannot make it in person
fear not you can scan the qr code and shop these brands from
home each got a good morning.
Good morning.
Happy fan fest.
This is so exciting.
This crowd.
Start with that.
We should use.
So Hoda is having her making space event tomorrow in Brooklyn where
she's going to have a conversation with Alicia Keys about different
stages in her life including the one where she started a beauty line.
It's called
key soul care.
This brand is really great in and of itself and
you know Alicia Keys is known for her glowy skin.
So it makes sense that her best
selling product is this beautiful.
Let it glow serum.
Let me go serum.
It's so lightweight.
It's moisturizing.
It's really great for the
morning when you're going to put on your makeup
because it also has illuminating properties.
There's three different shades that look great on
all skin tones.
And right now it's 30 percent off.
So it's just under 20 dollars.
So everyone needs one of these in their life.
OK. If you're
walking on the scene for fan fest you need some good.
Yeah.
So this is from our sponsor Fleet feet which is a running store.
And did you know most people are wearing the wrong size shoe.
So they're taking the guesswork out of it.
You can go into one of their stores and get your foot scan.
It's a 3D scan and they can measure it.
They measure the volume the width the length
all the things you can get the perfect fit.
And right now you can get these ultra shoes are
all their shoes on their site are free shipping.
We love the ultra sneakers because these are lightweight.
And if you're not a runner these are
really great if you're a walker to and our team loves these
insurers by the OK to really cute colors for men and women
as well.
What's this OK this is the cricket have you ever heard
of this I have not OK so I'm going to get you into crafting
because I use this for my wedding 6 years ago to do a
ton of our decorations,
it's a cutter and right now the
cricket maker you can get 20 dollars off a bundle on their
website starts at a $179.
It cuts over 300 different types
of fabrics materials everything from like a thin wood to
leather you can make he changed,
you know who really loves
these teachers,
okay,
my sister loved it too she makes a ton of
you have this stuff we made all this stuff you can jazz up your
paddleboard over here you can make pumpkin you can make
stickers you might be on my abilities,
but a great deal.
This is exactly and you can cut so many different things you
can craft up teachers love it people who have small businesses
really like this that device as well okay,
and that's you can
make some great holiday get all right.
Yeah,
okay,
this is from free scape so this is actually a shop
today sleep award winner for betting so they make a really
great breathable lightweight comforter if you're a hot
sleeper this is the brand for you this is for Craig yeah,
but we've got Dylan in the studio is testing out what he
sleeping on the job.
I want to be where she is cozy she is going to be and right now
you can take advantage about 20% off all of their stuff right
now so we can also get the sheets to which are just $80.
I mean feel how soft this yeah,
I decided so it's breathable
it's moisture waking your hot sleeper this is the brand.
Okay,
I've got some shots for you so I take your espresso shot
in the morning to wake up you're going to want some dough so
this is a really popular to Merrick supplement going to
get yet take it to the clue it.
Oh good.
We'll never learn okay,
so this is really great because it's packed with tumor a
ginger milk this all all these really great things for your
liver health.
Doctors who say tumor can help with reduce
inflammation,
I know with any supplement make sure you talk
to your doctor before you started this is really great
right now the expectations that doesn't taste it's really bad.
Yeah, I think Craig the fan to okay.
Okay last but not least
MNM love MNM did you know they make personalized MNM this is
a great gift for the holidays,
they're going to sneak up
before you know it you can get them customized with your name
you can even get clip are you can even put photos on
this and right now they're doing 20% off site wide
I'm saying I'm stuck in stocking up for Halloween.
but get some for
the holidays really cute get out and thank you if you want
to shop the stand best brands you can scan the qr code or go
to today dot com slash shop today has earned a commission
on purchases made through our links which you knew that back
in a moment, this is today on NBC.
But wait there's more Savannah.
This is rolling on the 4th hour for some super fan makeover.
First of all our today's shot today,
the favorites after local
news.
Hey thanks for watching don't forget you can catch the today
show every morning on NBC or take today when you're on the
go just follow the today podcast on Apple
podcast Spotify or wherever you listen.